this is a game where I drop a
celebrity's name and you have to say the
first thing that comes to mind you're
the perfect guest to play this game
first thing that comes to mind or a
funny story you have or a moment that
you wish never happened okay so the
first person
Russell Simmons
rapist
damn they got real I thought you were
going to talk about deaf Comedy Jam and
he's a liar
damn this game got real okay well okay
the next person now I used to work with
this person for a little bit
Kanye
well not Candace Owens first thing to
come to mind with Candace Owens and
Kanye
meds I don't know her
I'm laughing at that I don't know her
bro but don't you feel like is there any
space to ever forgive Kanye again
oh there's always space for Redemption I
think to a certain extent but you have
to acknowledge your error of your ways
I know I know about that man on a whole
other level though yeah so because I
know people that worked for him yeah and
I know that he doesn't treat the people
that work for him that way in a kind
like he doesn't have regard for them in
the way that he should as an employer
foreign